Robert A. Rose 6182 Waterman Blvd, St Louis, MO 63112 314-224-5583

robertrosestl67@gmail.com

Linkedin.com/in/robert-a-rose https://github.com/rarose67

SKILLS:

Languages

Proficient in: Python, Java, and JCL

• Familiar with: C#, CLIST, and REXX

Software

Database: MySQL

OS: Microsoft Windows

Other: Spring, Hibernate, Thymeleaf, MySQL, Flask, HTML, CSS.

POJECT EXPERIENCE

Blogz

A school project completed in LC101, it allows users to signup, create, and read blog posts.

- Python, Flask, SQLAlchemy, Jinja, MySQL, and HTML
- Beyond the assigned tasks, I included a feature that allows users to delete, or edit their owned blog posts
 - https://github.com/rarose67/blogz.git

Stock-dividend Simulator

A school project in LC101 I am currently building. It will allow user can take a portfolio of stocks that give dividends and determine how many shares of those stocks they will have after reinvesting the dividends for so many years.

- IEX API, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, and Bootstrap
- https://github.com/rarose67/stocks-java.git

WORK EXPERIENCE

DXC.TECHNOLOGY (formerly CSC)

Professional System Engineer

July 2010-August 2017

- I coordinated with a team of 10+ members to implement standardized set of software programs and replicate to 10+ clients. These programs ranged from operating system software to database related programs, debugging tools, as well as other products. Completed several of these projects each year.
- Installed, upgraded, customized, and maintained software programs on client systems
- Participated in software replacement resulting in cost savings to clients
- Solved issues for 10+ clients in coordination with team members and Service Delivery staff

Associate Systems Consultant December 2005-June 2010

- Installed multiple programs on client mainframes
- Assisted team with a Syspoint compiler project and IBM software scrub

 Consulted with team members and Operations and Delivery staff to solve client issues

EDUCATION

University of Missouri-Columbia

Columbia, Missouri

August 2000-December 2004

• BS Computer Science

LC101

January 2018 - June 2018

- 20 week program that focuses on programming fundamentals, web basics, and more advanced concepts with Java.
- Curriculum covered: Python, Flask, Jinja2, SQLAlchemy, MySQL, Java, Spring, Hibernate, and Thymeleaf
- Built multiple in class projects